[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Wizard of Oz, the part of Dorothy was played by Hollywood legend Judy Garland. How old was Judy during the making of the movie?", "correct_answer": "16", "incorrect_answers": ["22", "18", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many terabytes did ILM use for the making of the special effects in Transformers 2, compared to the 15 terabytes for the previous movie?", "correct_answer": "140 terabytes", "incorrect_answers": ["95 terabytes", "50 terabytes", "30 terabytes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of teacher Alastor Moody in the 2005 movie Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?", "correct_answer": "Mad-Eye", "incorrect_answers": ["Nest-Hair", "Lazybrains", "Fat-Lip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first American to ascend all fourteen peaks over 8,000m without oxygen?", "correct_answer": "Ed Viesturs", "incorrect_answers": ["Reinhold Messner", "Peter Habeler", "George Mallory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the euro become the official currency of the Eurozone?", "correct_answer": "2002", "incorrect_answers": ["1999", "1994", "2004"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the number of the bowling lane Rosie bowled in in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "18", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "4", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Hungarian-born American nuclear physicist, called the father of the hydrogen bomb, was a member of the Manhattan Project .", "correct_answer": "Edward Teller", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Oppenheim", "Stanislaw Ulam", "Albert Einstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What musical instrument made jazz performer Lionel Hampton famous?", "correct_answer": "Vibes", "incorrect_answers": ["Trombone", "Drums", "Clarinet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dreamgirls earned eight nominations in 2007, but not one for Best Picture. When was the last film before Dreamgirls with so many nominations that failed to also capture that top nomination?", "correct_answer": "1973", "incorrect_answers": ["1984", "1956", "1927"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Epic Movie, the character Peter is a spoof of what popular movie?", "correct_answer": "X-Men", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman", "None of these", "Superman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fictional town in which the movie Scream is set?", "correct_answer": "Woodsboro", "incorrect_answers": ["Woodsmith", "Woodstock", "Woodston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During World War II, Americans increased their popcorn consumption three times, because this product was not as widely available as it had been prior to the war.", "correct_answer": "Sugar", "incorrect_answers": ["Potatoes", "Nuts", "Nachos"]}]